celebwhiteteethshop.com 2010-03-12

# Privacy Policy

**Effective Date: Thursday, January 7, 2010**

The operator of this web site (“Site”), {{ corp_name }} (“Company” or “we”), has created this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect and use personal and certain other types of information about individuals (“you”) who access and interact with this Site.

## By accessing, using, placing an order, or otherwise interacting with this Site, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy.  IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THIS WEB SITE OR PROVIDE PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US THROUGH THIS WEB SITE.

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify this Privacy Policy at any time.  If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page of the Site and update the “Effective Date” at the top of this Privacy Policy so that you can always find out what information we gather, and how we might use that information.  We encourage you to periodically review our Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are using the personal information we collect.  Your continued use of this Site after any changes have been posted constitutes your agreement to the changes.

This Site is not intended for visitors that are under eighteen (18) years of age.   The Company does not knowingly solicit or collect information from individuals under the age of eighteen (18) years old.

**What Information is Collected?**

_Personal Information_

We collect personal information that is voluntarily provided to us when you enroll in our trial offer, purchase product, or otherwise interact with the Site in a manner that requires you to provide such information to us.  The personal information we collect may include, without limitation, your name, physical address, mailing address, shipping address, billing address, email address, birth date, credit card number, credit card expiration date, other billing information, username, password, and on occasion a unique identifier (for account security purposes). If you send any personal communication or correspondence, by any means, to the Site, or any of our employees, agents or representatives, the Site may collect additional information regarding that communication and include that information in our customer database.

_Non-Personal Information and Cookies_

We may collect certain non-personal information you, including but not limited to, browser type, operating system, IP address, and the referring domain from which you accessed our Site.  Non-personal information is information that does not personally identify you and is not associated with personal information about you.  Other non-personal information we may collect includes browsing behavior, date and time of visit, the pages visited; the time spent viewing the Site, return visits to the Site, and click-stream data. We do not track any information about you once you leave the Site. We may use cookies to collect this non-personal information. We may also allow unaffiliated third parties, such as advertisers and marketing partners, to serve cookies as well. You are always free to decline cookies, but in doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on our Site.

How Do We Use Information Collected About You?

We collect personal and non-personal information so that we may custom tailor the web experience for you and other visitors of this Site in order to offer the best products and services to meet your needs.

We may use personal and non-personal information collected from you for any of the following purposes: (1) to send you information and promotional materials about our products and services as well as the Company in general, which will not continue if you opt out of this service, (2) to send you information and promotional materials from our marketing partners and third parties, which will not continue if you opt out of this service, (3) to deliver targeted display advertisements and offers by email, which will not continue if you opt out of this service, (4) to contact you when necessary about your order or for other business or marketing purposes, (5) to facilitate your shopping experience and use of the Site by, for example, pre-populating customer fields within checkout, registration or other transaction processing screens, with your customer information as you may have previously provided it to us, (6) to help diagnose problems with our server, (7) to administer our Site, (8) to conduct internal reviews of our Site, (9) to help us better understand visitors’ uses of our Site, (10) to protect the security or integrity of our Site, and (11) for any other purpose that may be specified at the time of collection.

The Site is not responsible or liable for the use of any information that is gathered by third-party websites that have ads or links on the Site. This Site does not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or Privacy Policies of any of those third-party websites. Whenever applicable, you should read the Privacy Policy of any third-party website that you may visit.

**With Whom Do We Share Your Information?**

In addition to any other information sharing or disclosure practices described in this Privacy Policy, we may share your personal and non-personal information with third party contractors or service providers who assist us with the preparation and mailing of our marketing communications, and with order processing and fulfillment functions. For example, we may disclose your billing information to payment processors to process fee payments or other financial transactions; we may disclose your shipping address to fulfillment and shipping contractors to deliver a product to you; and, we may disclose your email address to email fulfillment contractors to send you emails from us. 

We may occasionally provide your personal information to carefully-screened marketing partners or other third parties for the purpose of contacting you with marketing and other information about products, services, or publications in which we believe you may have an interest. If you do not wish for us to share your personal information with such third parties, please write to: {{ corp_name }} - {{ corp_address }}, {{ corp_city }}, {{ corp_state }}, {{ corp_zip }} .

We may share some or all of your personal information with our subsidiaries and affiliates, joint venturers, or other companies under a common control (collectively, “affiliates”), in which case we will require these affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.  If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the personal information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or to comply with valid legal process (such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order), to protect the company’s rights or property (including without limitation in the event of a transfer of control of company or substantially all of its assets), or during emergencies when safety is at risk.

**How Do We Secure Your Information?**

We have implemented reasonable security measures to protect the personal information we have collected about you from unauthorized use, misuse, disclosure, loss and alteration.  Regarding all credit card and other purchase transactions, the credit card and other purchase information you provide to us is transmitted for processing via SSL encryption technology, which is the current standard in Internet encryption. As for all other information, you should consider this communication and information to be non-confidential, and consequently, we assume no responsibility or liability if any information relating to you is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient.

**How Can You Access or Correct Your Information?**

To access the personal information that this Site has collected about you, to correct factual errors in such information, or to update our records with respect to your personal information, please contact us using the information provided below.

_Privacy Rights of California Residents:_   Companies that collect personally identifiable information from California residents and disclose such information to third parties (including affiliated entities) for marketing purposes must, in response to a request by a consumer, either (1) provide a list detailing the categories of information shared and the entities to which such information was provided, or (2) provide a mechanism by which a consumer may opt-out of having his or her information shared with third parties. We have elected the second option, and you may request that your personally identifiable information not be shared with third parties by sending your request, including your full name, email address and postal address, to: {{ corp_name }} - {{ corp_address }}, {{ corp_city }}, {{ corp_state }}, {{ corp_zip }} .  California residents are also entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, Suite 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to [dca@dca.ca.gov](mailto:dca@dca.ca.gov).

**Contact Us**

{{ corp_name }} - {{ corp_address }}, {{ corp_city }}, {{ corp_state }}, {{ corp_zip }}
